<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on crystal&#39;s thoughts</title>
    <link>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on crystal&#39;s thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BLM</title>
      <link>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/blm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/blm/</guid>
      <description>June   June 2, 2020 - Oprah Magazine article listing Black-owned businesses to support
 Since the beginning of the pandemic, people have been trying to support small/local businesses. With the publicity of the BLM movement, more people have been advocating to support Black-owned businesses. This is an article from Oprah Magazine that lists several Black-owned brands to shop, and there are many more resources readily available to find more businesses to support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL</title>
      <link>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/global/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/global/</guid>
      <description>April  April 4, 2020 - Forbes article on China&amp;rsquo;s concentration camps  June  June 18, 2020 - @soyouwanttotalkabout post about the Yemen crisis  July  July 3, 2020 - Business Insider article on Lebanon entering a famine in the midst of the pandemic  Lebanon has been suffering through an economic crisis before the pandemic, but COVID-19 has made their situation significantly worse. With severe inflation, many people cannot afford to buy food and other nessecary goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/politics/</guid>
      <description>June   June 12, 2020 - NPR article on Transgender health rights
 The Trump administration has decided to allow discrimination against LGBTQ+ individuals in the health care system and health insurance. I find it disgusting that anyone has the power to not provide health services to someone based on their gender identity or sexual orientation. Not only is this a matter of dehumanizing a group of people, but this is even more of a major concern because we are currently in a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOCIETY</title>
      <link>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/society/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crystalkimm.github.io/posts/society/</guid>
      <description>April   April 21, 2020 - Refinery29 article about fast fashion
 Fast fashion is something that I rarely think about because shopping for clothes at stores like Urban Outfitters seems so normal to me. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been shopping much during quarantine, but when I return from my shopping hiatus, I hope to look into thrifting, renting, and buying second-hand items.    April 29, 2020 - Medium article on how Amazon is unethical</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>